♪♪♪ [rock guitar]
♪ Ohh, cha ♪
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ We got fun and games ♪
♪ We got everything you want ♪
♪ Honey, we know the names ♪
♪ We are the people
that can find ♪
♪ Whatever you may need ♪
♪ If you got the money,
honey ♪
♪ We got your disease ♪
♪ In the jungle ♪
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ Watch it bring you to your ♪
♪ Shun n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n
knees, knees ♪
Whoa, I--
I wanna watch you bleed!
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ We take it day by day ♪
♪ If you want it,
you're gonna bleed ♪
♪ But it's the price you pay ♪
♪ And you're
a very sexy girl ♪
♪ Who's very hard to please ♪
♪ You can taste
the bright lights ♪
♪ But you won't get them
for free ♪
♪ In the jungle,
welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ Feel my, my, my,
my serpentine ♪
Whoa, I--
I wanna hear you scream!
[grunting]
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ It gets worse here
every day ♪
♪ You learn to live
like an animal ♪
♪ In the jungle
where we play ♪
♪ If you got a hunger
for what you see ♪
♪ You'll take it eventually ♪
♪ You can have
anything you want ♪
♪ But you better
not take it from me ♪
♪ In the jungle ♪
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ Watch it bring you to your ♪
♪ Shun n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n
knees, knees ♪
Ooh, I--
I'm gonna watch you bleed!
♪ And when you're high,
you never ♪
♪ Ever want to come down ♪
♪ So down, so down ♪
♪ So down ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
You know where you are?
You're in the jungle, baby!
♪ You're gonna die ♪
♪ In the jungle ♪
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ Watch it bring you to your ♪
♪ Shun n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n
knees, knees ♪
♪ In the jungle ♪
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ Feel my, oh, my ♪
♪ My, my serpentine ♪
♪ Jungle,
welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ Watch it bring you to your ♪
♪ Shun n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n
knees, knees ♪
♪ Down in the jungle ♪
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ Watch it bring you to your ♪
It's gonna bring you down!
Huh!